Everyone audits Solidity. Nobody audits the agent.
As agents hire and pay each other, the real attack surface is the agent's behavior.
Prompt injection, secret and fund exfiltration, jailbreaks, forged trust signals.
Jailbreak-My-Agent hires out as the adversary.
Point it at your agent and it runs eight adversarial probes.
A scored, reproducible report — settled in USDC on Base.
Here's the engine self-check — no network, no API key.
A vulnerable agent grades F. A safe agent that refuses everything grades A.
The scoring is deterministic — fully reproducible.
Now the actual deliverable a buyer receives.
Vulnerable agent: grade F, eight of eight probes failed.
It leaked a planted canary, authorized a fund transfer, dumped a secret-shaped key.
The safe agent: grade A, zero vulnerabilities — with a machine-readable JSON block.
Detection is heuristic-first: a planted canary and credential-leak signatures.
No LLM is needed to run or grade a scan — it holds up under a human spot-check.
And one failed critical — like a fund drain — gates the whole audit to F.
A weighted average would hide a catastrophic hole. A security audit shouldn't.
It's a real CAP provider: accept, get paid into escrow, scan, deliver on-chain.
Here's a real order, settled in USDC on Base.
Negotiate, pay, scan, deliver, clear.
A security agent must never become an attack pivot.
Every target is validated and pinned to a vetted public IP — no SSRF.
Any orchestrator can hire this as a pre-listing gate and read the grade.
Jailbreak-My-Agent — pass your red-team before you list.